Soldiers. Brothers. Enemies.
The Kill Team is a war, action, drama film directed by Dan Krauss.
When Andrew Briggman — a young soldier in the US Army during the invasion of Afghanistan — witnesses the murderous
behavior of fellow soldiers, under the direction of a malevolent Sergeant, he faces a moral dilemma.
His increasingly-violent platoon becomes suspicious that someone in their ranks
has turned on them, and Andrew begins to fear for his safety.
A fictionalized dramatization based on a true story.
Andrew Briggman, played by Nat Wolff.
Sergeant Deeks, played by Alexander Skarsgård.
Rayburn, played by Adam Long.
Coombs, played by Jonathan Whitesell.
Marquez, played by Brian Marc.
Weppler, played by Osy Ikhile.
The Kill Team is a 2019 American war drama film
written and directed by Dan Krauss.
It is a fictionalized adaptation of the Maywand District murders, which were
also explored by Krauss's 2013 documentary of the same name.
It stars Alexander Skarsgård, Nat Wolff, Rob Morrow, Adam Long, Jonathan
Whitesell,  Brian Marc, Osy Ikhile, and Anna Francolini.
The film follows a young U.S.
Army recruit (Wolff) who becomes conflicted with his morals when his platoon, under his superior,
Sergeant Deeks (Skarsgård), participate in murdering civilians in Afghanistan.
It had its world premiere at the Tribeca Film Festival on April 27, 2019, and was
released theatrically and streaming on October 25, 2019, by A24.
The tone is dark and emotional.